lee yon e
kim yong gwan
and also Park Yoon Woo
drowned by the ice
all names and events are fictitious
any coincidences are random
drug use is a crime
which entails the destruction of personality
and also negatively affects your 7 and the environment
yes you promised
that by the end of the term the interest rate will be 3 and a half
so why are you talking about 3 now?
and to receive an additional rate of half a percent
you must have deposited at least 500,000 won within six months
however, during all this time you contributed only 200
there was no such thing
oh you dirty swindlers
return my money
why am I sir hello go
here you go
so sir
I want to offer you this
why is it a savings account with an interest rate of 2 and 5
but when using our credit card
you will receive an additional 3%
and that will be 5 and a half percent that
and what is the catch?
for those who are already the owner of our card
need to spend 10,000,000 per year
but if this is your first time receiving our credit card
then for you the amount of mandatory expenses will be only 5,000,000
no, I'm not interested at all
I see you already spend more every year with our regular card
but when using a credit card
you will also receive additional interest on your deposit
oh well
also on the occasion of your 60th birthday
you are exempt from taxes
isn't it great
it would be possible to receive a higher interest rate
and tax benefits
I but probably
congratulations in advance
well yes yes thank you
and thank you
have a nice day
it was you who gave the heat too
I issued a credit card
it's legendary
Have you raised your voice at least once in your life?
oh you beast
stop
catch them
such assholes
give me my money back you bastards
episode 4
who was it
you fool, admit it
tell me your name
what did you say
I don't remember anything
stop being a fool tell me
and how was I supposed to know?
why did they grab it?
I'm asking you
what do you allow yourself
concentrate
don't touch me
I really don't know anything
Mr. Policeman
it's all his fault
damn as much as possible
damn fool
art teacher
where are you really?
did you think of going to the police station
get out of there now
we'll do it as you wanted
just get out of there
come out quickly
damn
madam follow him
what a mess
shinchang who's next
hey there seemed to be a woman sitting with a bag
where is she and what is it
then girl
come on in
here talk to her
she's really sick
don't want to die
so what then
tell me already
Why are you silent? How were you going to get out?
shut up, I'm not old enough yet
what
I thought I'd be running on tiptoes forever
refreshing with you
looked down on me
I'm sick right
you are so unfamiliar with the feeling of compassion
what do you think will happen to my family
if I give away the goods
we'll die on the street
and you don't care
why should I sympathize with you
Am I your son or what?
when did you and I become a family?
why should I help you?
all these problems of yours
yeah I don't care about them
bastard, what did you hope for?
that I'm kind
it's for the better
anyway you won't be able to trade in jellyfish for a while
except jellyfish for me
and nowhere to sell
Cannes is full of other sellers
James where are you now
hear
you're finished
damn it
My husband's treatment and mortgage payment costs 186,000,000
that's all I need to worry about
I'll earn 200,000,000 and leave
all that remains is yours
will you go or are you against it?
seriously
the rest is for me
gwangjin station
here you lost the signals
I don’t believe you, remember about 1000000000
prove it's true
We will earn 100,000,000 in 2 weeks
then we'll talk
Let's test your skills in partnership
what if you do something behind my back again?
I'll show that video to your daughter
as you said, let's die together
Let's see who gets hurt more
will go
ok
decided
ну ты вообще конечно
shopping list
there are many ways
you can snort
dissolve in water or smoke through a pipe
the most effective way to administer into a vein
but I don't recommend it
why
you'll get used to it quickly
and your brain
will become mush, marks will appear on your hands
speech will become slurred
and everyone around is like that
and he's a drug addict
and then the police guys will come and grab you
and maybe us together
forgive me please
and there are others like that
I need to look and
don't sell to everyone
First of all, we must create a database of reliable clients
you need to learn to determine adequacy
in a couple of messages
especially you
ok
man yes I found it thank you
the product looks like a promotion
the price changes constantly
but on average from 50 to 80,000 per gram 1 word price
there are discounts
competition you know
recently I even took 100g for 15
means it is more profitable to sell fewer grams per
vacuum yes
but so much higher
risks the number of sales increases
the chance of getting caught increases
Wholesale sales bring in less profit
but they are safer
if the price per gram is 50 and sells for 20g per day
70,000,000 will be released in a week
we divide the profit 3-7
I will receive less than 100,000,000 per month
and if you sell it at 80 per gram
I will get 140000000
and in 1.5 months I will have 200000000
Do you have a calculator in your head?
We take new phones for sales
never use the cocoa current app
they'll figure you out right away
anyone can instantly hack such an application
download apps
that leave no trace
I understand the application
leaving no trace
are these notes
you can see
why are you crazy
I said you said it completely
no entries
just try to write something else down, stupid
do you know what perspective is?
yes you must understand the distance to the object
Vanishing point will help you with this
if all lines converge at 1 point
then this is a one-point perspective
we guarantee high quality and reliability
complete anonymity
high quality
purest product
отвечаем круглосуточно
did you see it
what was there
he photoshops his photos
seriously yeah
hashtag ice hashtag ice hashtag crystals something new
thank you
something has arrived
these are prohibited substances
I thought they started with the phrase good afternoon
can I ask
yeah screw
how much screw
it's about injections
unit of measure 1g
how much does 1 syringe hold? How to get it
delivery where
keep it short
if you're planning to buy
we need proof, drive proof
proof of identification or something that will confirm experience
well, to make sure that
he's not a bear
address ID card just in case and if it
they can always turn out to be scammers
what about you if he decides to rent us out or resell the goods?
we will not remain in debt
just like you
consultation
until you decide to tell the whole world about it
Let's decide on a place, dear
damn let's do it one more time
yes
god
I have a yellow belt
and yours is black
so you can kill
I told you to play sports
no but I
boss we can go
hey kyondo
let's go eat hey let's go eat
apparently
this is our James
rewind
who is this
there were a lot of people that day
I don't remember everyone
this is the first time I've seen them
a urine test will help you remember
but there is a warrant
funny
아
fuck you
look
this lady changed trains
she was always changing clothes and direction
what kind of bad luck is that
I don't bite, you brought a shocker anyway
come on faster
you'll try it yourself today
I'll take 3
please give me proof
you 1 we are first
they also ask me to give proof
what to do take a photo of your ID for him
so damn possible
Well of course not
did you listen to me at all
this is a setup
what what happened
suspected something was wrong and deleted the chat
stop worrying already
you choose your own insurance
Is there no need to explain anything to them? Answer right away
if you're too friendly
you will arouse suspicion
what the hell do you need 100000000
and by the way, you prepared the packaging
of course I came up with something
mom I'm home hi
what are you doing
phone fell behind the sofa help
both of you agree
obviously faster, right?
just work
arrange shipment within the country
please weigh your parcel
deliver the parcel
did you take something
it was interesting
I recently switched to this
they are simply amazing
let's try under them
hello hello
cash by card
Dohyun is so handsome good luck to you
I am a responsible executive
at my last job
colleagues
hwang dong hyun
I hope at my new job
James is gone
then find out who he worked with
numbers 34 and 35 you can come in
Stage 3 interview hello
let's start with lijin
introduce yourself
hello I'm Ligina number 34
Hello I'm Hwang Dong Hyun number 35
cop
I already told you everything
what else do you want from me?
hey young man
You can't spit on the street
what
have mercy don't kill
uncle, I really don’t know anyone or anything
no name, no number
no address, but that means I need to find out
then you'll get out of here
let me go
I will put my trust in him
no nonsense
konkhverim
hello khvirim it's me
I wanted to ask you
Do you know James' number?
who is your wrong number?
don't call herim anymore
now is not the time for jokes
Hello, I'll call someone else
I really don't know
who is he
please
I can call someone else
what wait
what is this for
don't keep your mouth shut please don't
what are you doing
saw seen
I really saw it
I saw a similar substance
they sell them online I'm not lying
let me in
have mercy
please
It has become more difficult to exchange cash
banking is too risky
if the transfer exceeds 10000000
bank requires confirmation
a fake identity will be required
about 6 at ATMs you can withdraw no more than 600,000 per day
and it’s not easy to forget to open an account these days
don't worry about it
leave it to me
working with money
all transactions must be carried out in bitcoins
login password
further
on different exchanges
We cash out our money in small amounts
James surgery completed
we receive a bonus for money laundering through the exchange
and withdraw cash from a fake account at an ATM
you can take the money
insert card
select operation
your request is being processed
you can take the money
wonderful
how much did I earn in jellyfish per day?
or per week
8 1000000000 is still far away
Do you think you'll have time to earn money?
Do you remember that there is less than a week left?
how much is there
300 more will be needed
we'll find
price
8000000
We won't drop 7 anymore
or go to others
mom phone
dozed off come here
group chat thank you
콜어크
delivery suits you
I'll check the product first
then money in cash
I'm afraid this is impossible
otherwise the deal is canceled
Do you remember that there is less than a week left, what to do
11 that's all
no 1 didn't come who
mom sua
this is already too much
how many meetings did she miss?
and the group chat doesn’t read at all
yes it's already
too
sua's parents are like parrots
lovebirds insu
It must be hard to hear the news about your husband's illness.
of course
agree professor yang
I'm away today don't wait up
officials and a good marriage are incompatible
this is the design
I don’t know much about apartment design
I visited factories
how much did it cost
boss
yaju
I've been wanting to try to do something like this for a long time
I love this show
you shouldn't have
the most important thing is to rest
everything is fine
that's what I came for
Insoo has a lot on his mind right now
I'm still her friend
that's why I want to help her
you're having a hard time because of me
who said that
It's not your fault that you got sick
people like you are worth their weight in gold
people like insu are even more valuable I'm lucky
you and her are like newlyweds
you have to
when will insu come
relax
let me sit in your place, you have an hour
rest room
room 203
I have some kind of meeting there
why so little
and so there are problems with money
how many shares do we have?
thuen groups less than 100,000
the share price today was 50,000
Your money can't even buy 1000
and you wanted at least 150
Austin thinks you already have everything
don't worry, this dog won't interfere with our business
I have some plan
next time I'll bring more money
Looks like bros
not at all interesting
where does this money come from
you don't even ask
yeah not interesting
the more I know you
the less I want to know
from experience
show money and ID on camera
check the ceiling in the bathroom
leave the money and take the goods
까꿍
ㅎㅎ
안나
why are you silent?
no outside
there is more
there's no one lying there
interesting
seller of such quality substance
turned out to be some kind of aunt
I agreed to your ridiculous plan
not because of pretty eyes
and not because I forgave
a
something is still interesting
are you still drawing?
aunty take off your mask
let's not even put a finger on you
let's touch and in return
you will sit quietly
until we leave with money and goods
not bad yes
6 no
I agree to 5000000
허음옳지
what's her name
infuriating b
I don't know
bye
gene
so that you don't think about it, make sure
that it won't harm the family
it will be awkward
if after all these years you get your ass
you understand
hey wait a minute
let's clink glasses
let's drink
Why did you sit down?
it will be awkward
if after all these years you get your ass
you understand
missed call
batter b konkhverim
yes hey I'm only for 2 minutes
I'm in a hurry
you can
come over now
now
oh you brutes
stop you assholes
hey you
you filthy bastards catch them
stand
return my money
give it back
give me my money back you bastards
아
why do you love insu so much
음
she's strong
well
soul
no matter how hard it is
whatever happens
she can't be broken
힘겨운소리차
벽이 무너지고
원샷이 팀장이
총알처럼아픈말
상처를 냈어
damn it, chase her
hey listen aunty
hey hey
Are you meddling bastard?
idiot
follow her, hey listen, get out
oh damn what is this sick guy doing?
bite her
you won't leave, you hear, you won't leave
shit
이제 쇼다
finally
caught
let's go
quickly
I'm really sick
what is it, let's run faster hey you
stop running
hey
your mom has already left
she's not at home
yes here too
got it thank you
now 1 has decided to die
where do you get this courage from?
I told you no personal meetings
especially alone
I had no choice
couldn't do it any other way
we have to earn money
me too
in the end everything worked out fine
yeah
money is great
but they can cost lives
they may try to take revenge
change your id and delete your account
by the way
how did you know that I was there
I installed the tracking app
yeah
the impudent guy is going crazy
by the way
Where did you learn to ride a scooter?
I worked part-time as a delivery driver in the same area
I know everything there
that's why you were always wrong there
and you prepared a lot
Well, of course I was preparing too
I liked her
here we actually met by chance
here you go
show me how much there is show me
we have to divide it
here you go
go to the hospital thank you
interesting
it's the teacher
this is our product
I see
I tried to find out who the seller is
but he deleted the account
or he's always careful
or something went wrong 1 of 2
we are searching the area around the store
from which the parcel was sent
but nothing yet
sorry
he wouldn't send someone like that out of his area
look for hanbok area
where would he die for us?
since this comrade
already changed id
check every huckster on telegram accounts
a
Are you still in contact with that rogue?
but after the kim min incident he didn't contact me
I don't know how many there are
but you have to find them
since so far I've only caught a mine
they
must consider themselves elusive
I'll do everything
while you're here, clean up nicely
height about 160
most likely a woman
unknown man
Panama hat
Panama hat and gray scarf accomplice
Gwangnam Transaction Venue
16th 0 accomplice
countdown from s to g telecom in new paxson juna
Kanansu resume
phone number
keep the price
I take it all
yeah okay just a minute
let's try for us
eat more
yeah
orthopedic pillows sell best
they are also popular abroad
she seems to really like it
mom this is just a bomb
really comfortable
really, you lie down too
try it too
well, how convenient it is
yeah nice so convenient
Mom just don't fall asleep
we're in the store
need to buy
they are very cool I like them
This car has a streamlined body shape
this makes it look like a sports car
let me open it for you
How do you like the interior? Quite roomy
Isn't it true that the meat is non-GMO, we take care of the quality?
mama sua this meeting
price 65,000 won
money must be returned by the end of the day
you can take it here
We heard that Haesung's brushes were stolen
Now I won’t leave anything in the classroom
and I found out who did it
no we don't know yet are you serious
wow this is a new model
oh the point is now the phone
you're lucky you won the lottery yes
what are you hinting at
Why are you so tense?
I just asked
you're lucky you won the lotto yes
what are you doing
your favorite stew
I'll cook it soon
are you home
who is it, let me see
are you here
let's add this
hi
your mom is home
drive me into danger
descendant of the cartoon
Have you heard about Nick James?
you seem to know each other
where is it
This is the James he's looking for
he's a bad person
but you are not with me
time left
promotion needed
need a name need a name
what did you do with that teacher
I saw you get out of his car
desperate people
the most terrible and the most evil
I want to kill them all
this is the best revenge